

About Me

Hello! I'm Gabriel Consolin.

I'm fullstack developer with 5+ years experience.

I worked on several frontend and backend frameworkds including React, NodeJS, VueJS, Angular, Laravel and so on

Age 27Residence Brazil

• Address Sao Vicente, Brazil

• e-mail gabriel.consolin2@gmail.com

• Freelance Available

Education

Universidade do Anhembi Morumbi

2012-2017 Universidade Inc.

In 1970, Anhembi Morumbi was founded as the first college in Brazil to offer higher education in the Tourism sector. Back then, many people did not quite understand the breadth of the Tourism segment, or even its importance to the country's economy. Concepts such as tourism potential and hospitality were introduced. And most importantly: a process of professional qualification started, which is increasingly valued in the labor market.

Experience

Fullstack-developer

Dec 2014 - Current BBD Participacoes

From Dec 2014 I worked as a fullstack-developer. I have experiences working with BBD Participacoes company

Frontend-developer

Dec 2012 - Dec 2014 Santander S.A. company

I worked with Banco Santander S.A. company.
I was suppossed to design and develop frontend web pages.

Frontend Skills



Backend Skills



My Services

PHP

fullstack frameworks including Laravel, Codelgnator and so on

Javascript

frontend: React, Vue, Angular

backend: NodeJS

Web Design

HTML5, CSS, jQuery and so on

Database

MySQL, MongoDB and so on

Portfolio

```
pelotas.rs.gov.br
                                //Laravel
compare.techtudo.com.br
                                //VueJS
serra.es.gov.br
                                //Laravel
meu.inss.gov.br
                                //React
sbcoaching.com.br
                                //Laravel
reclameaqui.com.br
                                //React
ecommerce.xpi.com.br
                                //VueJS
inss.gov.br
                                //DJango
ufrgs.br
                                //DJango
```















